{
    "subject": "resource/Today!_(Mississippi_John_Hurt_album)",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Vanguard_Records",
    "human_readable": "The label of Today! (Mississippi John Hurt album) is Vanguard Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9578681588172913,
            "question": "What is the name of Mississippi John Hurt's album released by Vanguard Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9256386756896973,
            "question": "What record label released the album 'Today!' by Mississippi John Hurt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8806130290031433,
            "question": "Who produced Mississippi John Hurt's album 'Today!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7387580871582031,
            "question": "Name an album by Mississippi John Hurt."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5964040756225586,
            "question": "What is the genre of Mississippi John Hurt's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5216572284698486,
            "question": "Which artist's album is titled 'Today!'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42735937237739563,
            "question": "Does Vanguard Records release other genres besides folk and blues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3736070394515991,
            "question": "What year was the album 'Today!' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34684616327285767,
            "question": "Who is the musical artist behind the album 'Today!'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22089625895023346,
            "question": "Is 'Today!' a popular blues album?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Today! (Mississippi John Hurt album) is Vanguard Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4189_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the musical artist behind the album 'Today!'",
            "html": "dbpedia_4189_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the album 'Today!' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4189_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Vanguard Records release other genres besides folk and blues?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4189_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4189_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents mentions that \"Today!\" is an album by Mississippi John Hurt and specifies the label as \"Vanguard\". Therefore, the statement that the label of the Today! (Mississippi John Hurt album) is Vanguard Records is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The album \"Today!\" by Mississippi John Hurt was actually released by Vanguard Records, not its label.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several passages explicitly state that \"Today!\" was released by Vanguard Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The label of Today! (Mississippi John Hurt album) is actually VRS 9220, not Vanguard Records.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provides detailed album credits, including the label information for \"Today!,\" which clearly states that it was released by Vanguard Records. Therefore, the label of Today! (Mississippi John Hurt album) cannot be incorrect based on the given information.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}